<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><atom:link href="https://unwarysage.github.io/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><title>Glimmers and Musings</title><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/</link><description>Charlots webshelf</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 01:35:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><generator>clj-rss</generator><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2021-03-17-wallflower-session-four/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2021-03-17-wallflower-session-four/</link><title>Wallflower Session 4: Chasing Smoke</title><description>A Brief Aside.The official campaign, No Room For A Wallflower is out. I'm reading through my copy and adapting the content to work with the canon I've established. So far, I'm finding the official version fixes most of the gaps in drafts I've worked around.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2021-03-09-wallflower-session-three/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2021-03-09-wallflower-session-three/</link><title>Wallflower Session 3: First Contact</title><description>Rise And ShineThe next morning, our pilots gather and check in.
Pilot Lyn's analysis program of the attacks and back-projected movements are consistent with a single sniper team.
Pilot Krell reflects about how steady the new recruits are with some satisfaction, even as they prep to pick up the
final two mechs, and discuss the upcoming mission with Castor Fielding.</description><pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2021-03-05-wallflower-session-two/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2021-03-05-wallflower-session-two/</link><title>Wallflower Session 2: Lasers In The Jungle</title><description>Breakfast And A ConversationWaking up, our three pilots meet Commander Hadura over breakfast. She spoke more about the sniper campaign,
and Zephyr started to collate the data that Commander Hadura and Patience could provide, in an attempt to model the movements of the sniper.
She also explained about the grey towns, the wildcat settlements formed from those who walked away from Patience's guidance to strike out on their own.
Officially, they are cut off, but unofficially there a thriving barter economy, Evergreen residents trading printer favors, and the grey towns providing non-staple foods. Jacob Merrick is a leader amongst these settlements.</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2021-03-02-wallflower-session-one/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2021-03-02-wallflower-session-one/</link><title>No Room For A Wallflower: A LANCER campaign</title><description>No Room For A WallflowerThe first official campaign for LANCER was a big part of what drew me to the system. I loved the story, as incomplete as the first drafts were, and knew I was going to run it someday. Post-graduation, I decided that time was now, and got together a small group of friends, trying to avoid my "everyone invited!" habits, and see what a smaller, more focused playergroup would be like. I am posting this shortly before No Room For A Wallflowers official release, and have been running the game from playtest drafts.
These logs are also summarized from player notes, and so are mostly from the players perspective.
All the same, there will be spoilers.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2021-02-17-blog-the-second/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2021-02-17-blog-the-second/</link><title>Blog The Second: Moving to Cryogen on Github Pages</title><description>ReignitionI hadn't touched this blog in a long time, but needing some projects to keep my skills up, I've decided to ressurect it.
However, I didn't want to go back to the standard GitHub Pages Jekyll workflow. I found my relative inability to tinker constraining,
as I didn't know the udnerlying language, namely Ruby. Jekyll is a fine project, but I'm principally a Clojure dev,
and I want to feel like I own my blog, and that means the code that powers it.</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-10-01-lonely-kingdom-unsought-deeps-2/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-10-01-lonely-kingdom-unsought-deeps-2/</link><title>Lonely Kingdom, The Unsought Deeps Log 2</title><description>PreviouslyThe party was united for better or worse, and sent along to the Dwarrow capitol,
placed under the observation of the Scholar Veidrie.
The previous session in full.</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-09-29-lonely-kingdom-dramatis-personae/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-09-29-lonely-kingdom-dramatis-personae/</link><title>Lonely Kingdom, Dramatis Personae</title><description>PreambleSorry for the silence, starting the semester blew a hole in a lot of my well laid plans. To recommence posting, I'm going to start putting my RPG groups (mis)adventure logs up on here. However, the campaign is a long form one, and so a lot of history has happened already. Let's start with the characters.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-09-29-lonely-kingdom-unsought-deeps-1/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-09-29-lonely-kingdom-unsought-deeps-1/</link><title>Lonely Kingdom, The Unsought Deeps Log 1</title><description>The Story So FarHaving been subcontracted into the fulfilling prophecies business, our intrepid heroes
had dabbled with dragons, dealt with demons, disappointed an angel, met a god, two kings, a prince and arrested one of them. They are seeking parts of the Omulkur, an artifact that has an almost ominous lack of legends associated with it.
They have secured one piece, in its shrine in the center of a labyrinth, and have in their possession a second piece: a pin, of grey-black stone, that utterly cancels and nullifies magic.
They seek its matching counterpart in the Underdark, based on the dying words of a burning halfling.</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-09-05-terrayiel-factions-and-power/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-09-05-terrayiel-factions-and-power/</link><title>Terrayiel, Factions and Power</title><description>|Previous: Souls and Magic|A Thin Peace</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-08-22-terrayiel-gods-and-the-church/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-08-22-terrayiel-gods-and-the-church/</link><title>Terrayiel, Gods And The Church</title><description>Previous: Overview|Next: Souls And MagicGods of the Twain Church</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-08-22-terrayiel-souls-and-magic/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-08-22-terrayiel-souls-and-magic/</link><title>Terrayiel, Souls And Magic</title><description>|Previous: Gods And The Church|Next: Factions and Power|Souls</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-08-20-terrayiel-a-dark-fantasy/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-08-20-terrayiel-a-dark-fantasy/</link><title>Terrayiel, A Dark Fantasy World</title><description>| Next: Gods and Legends |Terrayiel</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><guid>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-08-02-hello-world/</guid><link>https://unwarysage.github.io/posts/2018-08-02-hello-world/</link><title>Hello World!</title><description>HelloI'm about average height, I have shoulder length brown hair, eyes I'm told are hazel, a thin build and flat feet. On average, I'll be in a green t-shirt, jeans and maybe a flannel, probably rather rumpled. I go by They/Them/Their, and answer to Charlot.</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>